Proper sleep is essential to health.
What results have been obtained from 15 years of research on adult
sleep?
A University Hospital research team has observed 9,000 adults aged 40 to
60 for 15 years.
Sleeping more than 8 hours increased the risk of death by 27%
Less than seven hours of sleep was 11% higher.
There were also age-related differences.
When the age of 40 is low, over 60 are more vulnerable
to poor sleep.
The average Korean sleep time was 6 hours 58 minutes, 18% less
than the OECD average.
The daily rate of sleeping was only 7%, which was less than
half the global average.
The study team advised that regular sleep habits and a seven-hour period
of adequate sleep are key to maintaining good health.